Hell is for Heroes
Tunnel Rats is a action, drama, war film directed by Uwe Boll.
During the Vietnam War [1959-1975] a special US combat unit is sent out to hunt and kill the Viet Cong
soldiers in a man-to-man combat in the endless tunnels underneath the jungle of Vietnam.
Suicide squads of a special kind.
Sergeant Vic Hollowborn, played by Michael Paré.
Corporal Dan Green, played by Wilson Bethel.
Private Samuel Graybridge, played by Brandon Fobbs.
Private Terence Verano, played by Rocky Marquette.
Private Jim Lidford, played by Nate Parker.
Private Peter Harris, played by Mitch Eakins.
Tunnel Rats (also known as 1968 Tunnel Rats) is a 2008 war
suspense film written and directed by Uwe Boll.
The film is based on the factual duties of tunnel rats during the Vietnam War.
In a documentary for the film, Boll revealed the film did not have a
script, and instead the actors improvised their lines.
The box office return was poor but Tunnel Rats was met with positive reviews.
The tone is emotional.